<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>73739</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/73739-g4.jpg</banner>
<Overview>After their plane, Oceanic Air flight 815, tore apart whilst thousands of miles off course, the survivors find themselves on a mysterious deserted island where they soon find out they are not alone.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2004-09-22</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0411008</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH672362</zap2it_id>
<id>73739</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>72906</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost (2001)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/72906-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Three pairs of globe-trotting strangers must work together to be the first team to reach the Statue of Liberty from a secret drop location. The winners will split the prize of $200,000. Over the life of the series, two different adventures were scheduled to take place.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2001-09-01</FirstAired>
<zap2it_id>SH446649</zap2it_id>
<id>72906</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>182061</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Girl</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/182061-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Lost Girl focuses on the gorgeous and charismatic Bo, a supernatural being called a succubus who feeds on the energy of humans, sometimes with fatal results. Refusing to embrace her supernatural clan and its rigid hierarchy, Bo is a renegade who takes up the fight for the underdog while searching for the truth about her own mysterious origins.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-09-12</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt1429449</IMDB_ID>
<id>182061</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>72923</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost in Space</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/72923-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Lost in Space (1965 - 1968) is a science fiction TV series created and produced by Irwin Allen. 


A space colony family struggles to survive when a spy/accidental stowaway throws their ship hopelessly off course. </Overview>
<FirstAired>1965-09-01</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0058824</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH002675</zap2it_id>
<id>72923</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>80595</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost (UK)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/80595-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Of all the numerous reality game shows that enveloped British TV in the wake of Big Brother, Lost was one of the least publicised, low key, and most entertaining. The premise was ultra-simple. Three pairs of contestants were abandoned, blindfolded, somewhere in the world armed only with a meagre amount of possessions and a limited ration of local currency. They'd no idea where they'd been taken, and were deliberately deposited in as desolate, inhospitable and lonely environment as possible. They then had to get back to London as quickly as possible, and the first team home won a bottle of champagne - plus the chance to do it all again next week.

Various elements combined to make the participants' respective journeys hugely enjoyable television. There was our sometimes gruesomely intimate insight into the relationships between team members, as they worked with but often against each other and squabbled constantly over how to make progress. The isolation aspect was intensely tangible. Aside from just one solitary cameraman - who themselves often became part of the drama - each pair were utterly alone, and you really felt it. Then there was the fact it was a desperately tense race against time. For every nonchalant easy-going contestant there was another absolutely determined to win at all costs. Finally Lost showcased a hilariously haphazard style of globetrotting, involving chaotic hitching and hiking across whole continents to the utter bemusement of their inhabitants. A potent mix of fly-on-the-wall showmanship and epic adventure, Lost was an exceptional show unfairly tucked away late at night that always managed to impress and excite.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-09-27</FirstAired>
<id>80595</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73831</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Treasures of NFL Films</SeriesName>
<Overview>Welcome to the Lost Treasures of NFL Films guide at TV Tome. Since 1962, Steve Sabol has been an employee of NFL Films as a cameraman, an editor, a producer, and now its president.  It made him think he knew everything NFL Films had ever shot.  But co-worker Phil Tuckett's discovery of an unused film negative, led to the creation of this series.  Two years of searching the film vaults has turned up thousands of feet of unseen film footage. Steve Sabol, the host of Lost Treasures of NFL Films, foolishly thought he could produce one 60-minute documentary covering the whole history of NFL Films.  In fact, enough material was unearthed to cover five programs, all on the 1960s.  And it just expanded from there.  In addition to the five-part reflection of NFL Films' beginnings in the 1960s, Lost Treasures of NFL Films unearthed footage of minor-league football, TV football analysts, training camps, and much more.  The result totaled 22 episodes spanning four decades, airing on ESPN</Overview>
<FirstAired>1999-09-01</FirstAired>
<id>73831</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>134421</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Kingdoms of Africa</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/134421-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Four-part series in which British art historian Dr Gus Casely-Hayford explores the pre-colonial history of some of Africa's most important kingdoms.

The African continent is home to nearly a billion people. It has an incredible diversity of communities and cultures, yet we know less of its history than almost anywhere else on earth.

But that is beginning to change. In the last few decades researchers and archaeologists have begun to uncover a range of histories as impressive and extraordinary as anywhere else in the world.

The series reveals that Africa's stories are preserved for us in its treasures, statues and ancient buildings - in the culture, art and legends of the people.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-01-05</FirstAired>
<id>134421</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>160821</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Spain - Paradise Lost</SeriesName>
<id>160821</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>187681</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost in the pancake</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>1975-09-01</FirstAired>
<id>187681</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73181</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Universe</SeriesName>
<banner>text/22113.jpg</banner>
<Overview>400 years ago mankind advances to the stars. Researchers discovered Psychophysics, the application of mental power upon the laws of physics, and exceeded the speed of light for the first time in the 21st century. Mankind Inaugurates the Milky Way Union, and establishes the Universe Force to police it.  Kain Blueriver, a mantle clad Psy-Blade wielding Trouble Contractor, and Canal, the hard hologram AI of the spaceship SwordBreaker are joined by the ex-detective Mily on there adventures throughout the Milky way.  A fantastic Space Adventure by Hajime Kanzaka, the executive producer of The Slayers.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1997-07-01</FirstAired>
<id>73181</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>130231</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Chronology</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/130231-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Lost Chronology is the story of the crash of Oceanic flight 815. From the first day on the Island until day 108 when our beloved Oceanic Six were found. The story is told in chronological order from day 1 until day 108, simultaneously telling the story from all viewpoints of the major groups of people on the Island. The story of the Fuselage survivors, Tail section survivors, and The Others all unfold together in chronological order to tell the complete story of the Oceanic survivor's time on the Island.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-06-23</FirstAired>
<id>130231</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>194571</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Gardens</SeriesName>
<Overview>Step back in time to discover eight forgotten and overgrown gardens, recreating them to resemble what they would've been in their heyday.

Renowned British garden presenter Monty Don leads a horticultural and design team to ressurect eight very different British gardens, spanning 500 years.

They include a 19th century Warwick grocer's detached pleasure garden, a Tudor country pleasance and a piece of Edwardian Japanese pastiche.</Overview>
<id>194571</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82934</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost in Austen</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/82934-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Jemima Rooper stars as Amanda Price - the frustrated romantic who lives for reading and adores the characters in her Jane Austen books. Then one day she discovers a gateway in her flat and ends up being transported to her favourite world, the world of Pride and Prejudice. But is the “true” story in danger of being thrown off track by her presence?</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-09-03</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt1117666</IMDB_ID>
<id>82934</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82715</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Land of the Jaguar</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/82715-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>New series combining stunning wildlife with high octane adventure as a team of explorers search the depths of the last great unspoilt jungle on the planet.

Cameras follow the team every sweaty step of the way as they explore the beautiful wilderness of Guyana, from abseiling down one of the most powerful waterfalls in the world to climbing to the very top of the rainforest trees. Known as the land of giants, Guyana is home to the huge anaconda, the world's largest tarantula and giant otters</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-07-30</FirstAired>
<id>82715</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>109501</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Treasures Of The Ancient World</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/109501-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The unique Lost Treasures series enables the ancient wonders of the world to be seen as never before... magically ‘restored’ to their former glory by 3D graphics and presented in a superb animated format. Our camera teams have traveled the world to gather spectacular new footage of ancient history’s greatest monuments and their surroundings, providing a fascinating link between the past and the present day. Features superb 3D graphics, State-of-the-art computer generated animation, all new location footage, and expert commentary and analyses. Contains Ancient China, Ancient India, Samurai Japan, Empires In The Americas, Dark Age England, The Celts.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1998-01-01</FirstAired>
<id>109501</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>71225</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost on Earth</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>1997-01-01</FirstAired>
<id>71225</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>248705</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Special Lost</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/248705-g.jpg</banner>
<id>248705</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>83741</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Cities of the Ancients</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/83741-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Archaeologists are unearthing lost civilizations, forgotten histories and incredible technologies that date back thousands of years. Re-discover these amazing, forgotten civilizations and marvel at the cities and empires they built.</Overview>
<IMDB_ID>tt0871924</IMDB_ID>
<id>83741</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>155761</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>How The West Was Lost</SeriesName>
<Overview>The history of 19th-century America is the story of struggles between settlers moving west and Native Americans trying to hold on to their ancestral territories. The clash between lifestyles and land rights forged a new land and unified an American culture, but in the process a venerable way of life was destroyed. Follow the Cherokee, Dakota, Lakota, and Nez Perc as they fight to keep their homelands. </Overview>
<id>155761</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>85751</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Treasures of the Ancient World The Seven Wonders</SeriesName>
<id>85751</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>235361</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Buildings of Britain</SeriesName>
<Overview>Six part architectural history series considering six important British buildings which no longer exist, with computer use to reveal what they would have looked like.</Overview>
<IMDB_ID>tt0420423</IMDB_ID>
<id>235361</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>80525</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Civilizations</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/80525-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The secrets of lives once lived. Never before could you get so close to 7000 years of history! From the bloodletting of Maya kings and a pharaoh's last journey to the secret pleasures of a Roman empress. Original location cinematography in 25 countries takes you from Cuzco in Peru to Petra in Jordan. From ancient Mesopotamia to modern Tibet, lost worlds live again on these must-have DVDs!</Overview>
<FirstAired>1995-06-25</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0112054</IMDB_ID>
<id>80525</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>112631</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Land of the Volcano</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/112631-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>An international team of scientists, cavers and wildlife filmmakers venture deep into the heart of the remote tropical island of New Guinea to explore a giant extinct volcano - Mount Bosavi.

The team live deep in the rainforest and search for the rare and endangered creatures that hide in these forests.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-09-06</FirstAired>
<id>112631</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>71150</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost at Home</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>2003-04-01</FirstAired>
<zap2it_id>SH568742</zap2it_id>
<id>71150</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>74729</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Highway</SeriesName>
<Overview>Lost Highway: The History of American Country is a critically acclaimed BBC documentary series. Narrated by Grammy Award-winning Texas singer/songwriter/musician Lyle Lovett, the four-part series has been hailed by The Times (London) as "a fascinating road map of the genre." The series celebrates the history of country music, from its origins in the folk songs of the working classes of the South Eastern states to the multi-million dollar industry of modern Nashville.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2003-02-01</FirstAired>
<id>74729</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>191721</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost In Africa</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/191721-g.jpg</banner>
<id>191721</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>191491</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Land of the Tiger</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/191491-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Documentary following a team of big cat experts and wildlife filmmakers as they embark upon a dramatic expedition searching for tigers hidden in the Himalayan Kingdom of Bhutan.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-09-21</FirstAired>
<id>191491</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>145741</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost in The Nevada Triangle</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/145741-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>What does the mysterious disappearance of record-breaking aviator Steve Fossett have in common with Area 51? In September 2007, Fosset went missing somewhere over the Sierra Nevada mountain range, sparking the biggest peacetime search and rescue operation in the history of the United States. Over the ensuing days and weeks, reports would surface of dozens of other missing airplanes in a huge triangular area of California and Nevada. Could this mysterious region be another Bermuda Triangle?
</Overview>
<id>145741</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>118291</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Dinosaurs Of New Zealand</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/118291-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The discovery of New Zealand dinosaurs by retired housewife turned scientist Joan Wiffen is casting new light on the behaviour of dinosaurs during the Late Cretaceous and the puzzle of why dinosaurs in general became extinct.When retired Kiwi housewife Joan Wiffen went gemstone and fossil hunting with her late husband Pont back in 1972 she never imagined that she would be awarded an honorary PhD for discovering New Zealand's first dinosaur bones.</Overview>
<id>118291</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>115361</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Get Lost!</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/115361-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The plot of Get Lost! concerns the disappearance of Jim Threadgold (Brian Southwood), husband of English teacher Judy Threadgold (Turner). Aided by her colleague, woodwork teacher Neville Keaton (Armstrong), Judy sets out to find out what has happened to her husband. Judy and Neville soon discover the existence of a secret organization dedicated to assisting people who want to escape the mundanity of their lives and families and just disappear. Although Judy eventually finds her missing husband, she is none too enthusiastic about taking him back and allows him to seek a new life running a fish and chip shop. Her adversarial relationship with Neville blossoms into a love affair.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1981-09-22</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0081868</IMDB_ID>
<id>115361</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>89691</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost World of the Raj</SeriesName>
<Overview>A look back at life in British India under the Raj.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-06-15</FirstAired>
<id>89691</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>80685</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Worlds</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/80685-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Teaming with archaeologists and using cutting edge visual technology, Lost Worlds brings back to life lost civilizations and cultures. Join us on the quest to rebuild what was lost and is now found. From ancient Egypt, early Athens, Atlantis and even the Knight's Templar, Lost Worlds travels the world.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2005-04-04</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0962966</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH792856</zap2it_id>
<id>80685</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>79616</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Worlds, Vanished Lives</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/79616-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The study of rocks and their ancient secrets was something of a boyhood passion for David Attenborough. In these programmes, his enthusiasm for the subject is undiminished. With the help of expert palaeontologists, fossil hunters and (for the time) modern animation techniques, Attenborough attempts to show how life evolved in Earth's distant past. To do so, he travels the globe to visit the world's most famous fossil sites.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1989-04-23</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0764075</IMDB_ID>
<id>79616</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>189461</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Worlds Vanished Lives</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/189461-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The study of rocks and their ancient secrets was something of a boyhood passion for David Attenborough. In these programmes, his enthusiasm for the subject is undiminished. With the help of expert palaeontologists, fossil hunters and (for the time) modern animation techniques, Attenborough attempts to show how life evolved in Earth's distant past. To do so, he travels the globe to visit the world's most famous fossil sites.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1989-04-23</FirstAired>
<id>189461</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>98261</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Evidence</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/98261-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The History Channel series The Lost Evidence recounts the moments of key battles in the European and Pacific theaters through the use of recently unearthed reconnaissance photos that were taken during the actual battle as well as in the days and weeks prior. Interviews with men on both sides of each battle offer a fresh look at the war.

For the first time these original high-resolution images enable us to track the battles, step by step, from the air. Individual stories of courage and heroism can be placed in the exact location where they took place. Using cutting edge technology, unique archive film, vivid re-enactments and extraordinary interviews with the fighting men, we obtain a unique insight into the fighting that took place.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2004-06-07</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0815450</IMDB_ID>
<id>98261</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>71177</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Land of the Lost</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/71177-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Rick Marshall and his children Will and Holly were on a weekend expedition rafting trough a river when an enourmous earthquake diverts them to an eclectic alien world inhabited by dinosaurs, chimpanzee-like cavemen called Pakuni, and aggressive, humanoid creatures called Sleestak.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1974-09-01</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0071005</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH019123</zap2it_id>
<id>71177</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>109201</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost Inventions</SeriesName>
<Overview>A look at some of the inventions we consider modern, which actually appeared years before we think, from an early form of napalm to the first submarine.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-08-06</FirstAired>
<id>109201</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>179671</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Lost in China</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/179671-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>From China’s wild west to Beijing’s boom, photography and filmmaking duo Jeff and Peter Hutchens capture china in its moment of change.</Overview>
<id>179671</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>242381</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>How Hitler Lost The War</SeriesName>
<id>242381</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>101271</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Saint Seiya: The Lost Canvas – Hades Mythology</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/101271-g2.jpg</banner>
<FirstAired>2009-06-24</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>101271</IMDB_ID>
<id>101271</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>147511</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Atlantis: Secret Star Mappers of a Lost World</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/147511-g.jpg</banner>
<id>147511</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>144161</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost World of Friese-Greene</SeriesName>
<Overview>During 1924 and for the next two years, Claude Friese-Greene, filmmaker and cinematographer, embarked on an epic journey, and calling it The Open Road, which would bring the people and the lands of Great Britain together. From Land's End to Scotland's John O'Groats, and with his new and modern filming technique, that for once has the ability to film in colour. For the first time the people of England, and the world could see itself in colour. This modern-day retrospective looks back, and takes the same ride some eighty years later, reconnecting with past places and past memories. With its compare and contrast travelogue flavour, Dan Cruickshank, the British Film Institute and the BBC have revisited a journey of how we used to live and how, as a nation, have changed, since those glorious days of England's golden years. Wonderful colourful historical vision with its updated look into the past.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-04-18</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0804421</IMDB_ID>
<id>144161</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>83333</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>History's Lost &amp; Found</SeriesName>
<Overview>History's Lost and Found was a television show from the History Channel first aired in 1999. Each episode is divided into three different segments concerning a different "lost" item or artifact from history. Most of the time, the three segments do not relate. Each segment runs around 7 minutes and in this time we learn the history, of several famous lost artifacts such as the flags from the Battle of Iwo Jima, and other not so famous artifacts like the first TV Dinner tray. Some segments were reused in other episodes. Episodes of the show were released on VHS in 2001 and the first episode has been released on DVD. 2000 was the big year for the series as most of the episodes were created and aired during that year, but a few new episodes aired 4 years later in 2004.

</Overview>
<FirstAired>1999-08-07</FirstAired>
<id>83333</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>80333</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Tribes</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/80333-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Three Australian families travel to exotic locales only to be unexpectedly inserted into tribal cultures and told to assimilate. Can a modern family get in touch with their deep ancestral roots by donning loin cloths and learning out to hunt and gather?</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-05-06</FirstAired>
<id>80333</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>118221</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Jack Hunter and the Lost Treasure of Ugarit</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/118221-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Exciting treasure hunt in beautiful and dangerous Syria, Turkey and Egypt. High speed action and romance. Jack Hunter &amp; The Lost Treasure of Ugarit is an action packed miniseries that follows the adventures of a present day treasure hunter as he tries to uncover the location of The Star of Ugarit - an ancient weapon, sought after by the NSA and the Russian Mob.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-12-23</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt1069207</IMDB_ID>
<id>118221</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82250</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>WWII: The Lost Color Archives</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/82250-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>World War II has been seen as a black and white war... until now! The scenes are authentic. The color is real.

In the 1980s determined researchers began scouring the world for color film shot during World War II, and the result of their quest is spectacular. Seeing the war through the ubiquitous black-and-white footage has always made the experience somewhat distant, but in clear, crisp color, the enormity of the war and its horrors is startling and dramatic. Films of Nazi rallies are all the more disturbing; a viewer seeing the scene in color realizes the massive crowds saluting Hitler are no longer gray and faceless masses, but gatherings of well- dressed civilians. Color combat footage, from across Europe and the Pacific, is frighteningly immediate, and some of it, showing the wounded, the dead, and even prisoners being executed, will no doubt be disturbing for many viewers. Violence and destruction on an unimaginable scale is vividly put on display, as are smaller moments of soldiers smiling for the camera or liberated prisoners from the concentration camps staring in pained bewilderment. The episodes, produced by the History Channel, are introduced by veteran journalist Roger Mudd, and the narration for each individual segment typically contains excerpts from letters and diaries describing events close to those depicted in the film footage. The footage used is of a surprisingly high quality (much of it was shot and stored away, virtually unseen for decades), and it provides a stunning look at how the war appeared to those fighting it.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2000-07-05</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0275779</IMDB_ID>
<id>82250</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82275</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Gods</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/82275-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Sooner or later, everything ends.

One by one, the mighty civilizations of the ancient world passed into history. And when they died, their gods died with them. Or did they?

The Lost Gods, a documentary series that takes a thought-provoking look at these ancient empires and their vanished religions.

The Lost GodsProduced in partnership by Tile Films of Dublin and Toronto-based VisionTV International, The Lost Gods was shot on High Definition at locations in 11 different countries. The host is Irish author and television personality Christy Kenneally, who also crafted the script.

Each half-hour episode traces the rise and fall of one of the great civilizations: the Egyptians, the Greeks, the Romans, the Maya, the Inca and the Celts. Kenneally follows the evolution of each culture's spiritual beliefs, examines the art and architecture created to honour the gods, and reveals the ultimate fate of these empires and their religions. </Overview>
<IMDB_ID>tt1085203</IMDB_ID>
<id>82275</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>202111</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Quest For The Lost Civilisation</SeriesName>
<Overview>
In this set of three videotapes, writer Graham Hancock traverses the world and explains his controversial theory that an ancient civilization, highly intelligent people who sailed the planet as early as 10,500 B.C., spread advanced astronomical knowledge and built ancient observatories. Skeptics may scoff, but Hancock earnestly points out similarities in giant stone structures in the Egyptian desert and Cambodian jungles, and on Easter Island and in Micronesia, he points out what he considers evidence of an ancient society of seafarers. His ideas may seem utterly bizarre at first, but Hancock presents them in an understated and good-natured manner, and he also makes clever use of computer graphics and aerial photography to illustrate the startling similarities in ancient structures found from the North Atlantic to the South Pacific. At times the three documentaries overlap, and at times they seem like one long program rather than three separate presentations. But throughout, Hancock raises some puzzling questions, and even if you don't buy his arguments, bolstered though they are by mathematical equations and astronomical diagrams, the Quest for the Lost Civilization is an entertaining mixture of archaeology, astronomy, and speculation</Overview>
<FirstAired>1998-10-31</FirstAired>
<id>202111</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>81313</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Man who Lost his Head</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/81313-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Martin Clunes stars as a straight-laced museum curator who finds himself travelling to New Zealand to settle a dispute with a Maori community about an ancient carving - with unexpected consequences.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2007-08-26</FirstAired>
<id>81313</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>78687</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Brats of the Lost Nebula</SeriesName>
<Overview>When the world-destroying alien army The Shock invaded the home planet of young brother-sister duo Zadam and Triply, the youngsters' parents scuttled them off to the relative safety of the Lost Nebula. 
The kids landed on a living Planetoid and discovered three other homeless youths: Ryle, blue-skinned and a fierce competitor; Lavana, a fairy-winged mage; and Duncan, a musclebound tinkerer. The group banded together to fight The Shock as the Brats of the Lost Nebula.
&amp;lt;B&amp;gt;NOTE:Of the 13 episodes of Brats of the Lost Nebula, only the first three ended up airing on kids' WB. The last 10 episodes then debuted on the Canadian channel YTV.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1998-10-01</FirstAired>
<id>78687</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>79637</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Room</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/79637-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The series revolves around the titular room and some of the everyday items from that room which possess unusual powers. The show's protagonist, Joe Miller, is searching for these objects to rescue his daughter, Anna, who has disappeared inside the Room. Once a typical room at a 1960s motel along U.S. Route 66, the Lost Room exists outside of normal time and space since 1961, when what is only referred to as "the Event" took place.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-12-11</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0830361</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH875605</zap2it_id>
<id>79637</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>191901</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost City</SeriesName>
<Overview>A 1935 Serial. A mad scientist, Zolock, has created  natural disasters as a prelude to his attempt to take over the world. Scientist Bruce Gordon goes to a secluded area in Africa after realizing that the natural disasters are electrically induced from there. Here he finds Zolock, last of the Lemurians, in a secret complex under a mountain.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1935-03-06</FirstAired>
<id>191901</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>188791</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Askadis: The Legend of the Lost Empire</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>1982-05-05</FirstAired>
<id>188791</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>118841</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Phenomenon: The Lost Archives</SeriesName>
<Overview>A recently unearthed repository of materials formerly classified by the secret government....The Phenomenon Archives.
This series covers the taboo subjects which have had light shed on them by pouring over the materials in this repository</Overview>
<FirstAired>1998-10-15</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0232308</IMDB_ID>
<id>118841</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>90191</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost World Of Communism</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/90191-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Documentary series charting the collapse of Communism across Eastern and Central Europe. Ordinary people recount their extraordinary stories of life behind the Iron Curtain.</Overview>
<id>90191</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>156681</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>WWII, The Lost Films</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/156681-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The only ones to see war like this were the ones who lived it. Until now...

WWII The Lost Films is not just one of HISTORY's biggest projects, but one of the most ambitious productions ever undertaken in documentary television history. Over three thousand hours of high definition colour film (filmed in colour, not colourised) was discovered in locations all around the world. This dramatic footage has not been seen before and is the backdrop to the incredible personal stories of 12 American soldiers recounting their experiences of fighting in the war's biggest battles. Using the diaries of these men, WWII Lost Films creates a moving, personal and detailed look at life at the front lines. Diaries were illegal for U.S. soldiers to carry, but the 12 characters in this series hid them away in their packs and recorded their experiences in detail.</Overview>
<id>156681</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>183241</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Saint Seiya Lost Canvas</SeriesName>
<id>183241</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>179701</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Superfriends: The Lost Episodes</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/179701-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Powerful super heroes Batman, Robin, Superman, Wonder Woman, Aquaman, Wonder Twins Zan and Jayna.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1995-01-09</FirstAired>
<id>179701</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>112461</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Britain's Lost World</SeriesName>
<Overview>Historian Dan Snow, naturalist Steve Backshall and wildlife enthusiast Kate Humble set out to solve some of the mysteries of St Kilda in Scotland's Outer Hebrides - the only British World Heritage Site nominated for both its extraordinary history and its wildlife.
Inhabited just 80 years ago, St Kilda is now home to seabirds and seals but these islands remain a place of mystery. When the St Kildans suddenly abandoned their homes, they left behind a place full of secrets and Dan, Steve and Kate travel to these far flung islands to find out just who were the strange and remarkable people, why did they leave, and can St Kilda's amazing wildlife survive in the modern world?</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-06-19</FirstAired>
<id>112461</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>82834</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Xam'd: Lost Memories</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/82834-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Akiyuki, the main character of the animated series, lives on Sentan Island, a land that has preserved its status as a free and peaceful island in a world consumed by fighting between the Northern and Southern Governments. All of this changes when Akiyuki boards a bus along with a mysterious white-haired girl who transforms his arm with the lost memories and power of Xam'd.

As Xam'd, Akiyuki goes on a rampage and is saved when a foreign girl with red hair named "Nakiami" calms him down, taking him back to her postal vessel. Akiyuki now must gain control of his powers and use them against the Northern Government's latest weapons, known as "Humanforms". Traveling the world on a postal vessel, Akiyuki hopes to return home one day, but until then he befriends other passengers on the boat.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-07-15</FirstAired>
<id>82834</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>76861</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Land of the Lost (1991)</SeriesName>
<Overview>The Porter family, Tom, Kevin, and Annie get sucked into a prehistoric alternative world while taking a family vacation. The Porters build a tree house, hook up with a few locals, Tasha- orphaned, extra smart dinosaur, Stink-monkey man, and Christa-another human who has lived in the Land of the Lost since she was a little girl. The Porters must deal with living with dinosaurs and avoiding the evil advanced Sleestaks.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1991-09-01</FirstAired>
<id>76861</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>84482</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Prince</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/84482-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Poignant historical drama telling the story of the youngest child of George V and Queen Mary, an epileptic with learning difficulties who was unable to take part in public life.

The film won a high viewing figure and much praise, was released on VHS and DVD and was repeated on BBC One in January 2004.

Both Miranda Richardson and Gina McKee received Best Actress nominations at the British Academy Television Awards in April 2004. The miniseries was also nominated for BAFTA TV awards for editing (Clare Douglas), music (Adrian Johnston), and photography (Barry Ackroyd).

When the production was transmitted in the United States in October 2004, it won the Emmy Award for Outstanding Miniseries in 2005. Miranda Richardson was nominated for a Golden Globe.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2003-01-01</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0349747</IMDB_ID>
<id>84482</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>102711</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Rebels and Redcoats: How Britain Lost America</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/102711-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Historian Richard Holmes brings us the extraordinary story of America's first civil war. We've been told that the War of Independence was the American people's struggle for liberty against an oppressive colonial power. However, many Americans were loyal to the British Crown throughout the war; men and women often chose sides not because they wanted freedom, but because they wanted their neighbour's land. Using vivid reconstruction, eye-witness accounts, original documents and paintings, and Richard's proven story-telling skills, this film overthrows traditional perceptions about these compelling years. As the story unfolds, the truth emerges - a truth far more fascinating than we were ever led to believe.</Overview>
<IMDB_ID>tt0433440</IMDB_ID>
<id>102711</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>81028</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Tomb of Jesus</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/81028-g.jpg</banner>
<id>81028</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>106401</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Byzantium: The Lost Empire</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/106401-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>John Romer recreates the glory and history of Byzantium. From the Hagia Sophia in present-day Istanbul to the looted treasures of the empire now located in St. Marks in Venice. 
</Overview>
<FirstAired>1997-03-01</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0344994</IMDB_ID>
<id>106401</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>78457</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost World</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/897-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>At the dawn of the 20th century, a band of adventurers are part of an expedition to prove the existence of a lost world isolated from the modern world. Disaster happens and the band find themselves trapped and isolated in this dangerous land with only the help of a young wild woman who was stranded in the land herself as a child. Together, the band fight to survive against the fearsome dinosaurs and other dangers that land has as they search for a way to escape. The Lost World reruns are currently airing on TNT every morning at 6:00am eastern standard time. Replays are also still continuing in syndication.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1999-04-01</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0240278</IMDB_ID>
<id>78457</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>83797</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Secrets of Lost Empires</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/83797-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Secrets of Lost Empires is a two part television series produced by PBS Nova, Boston (WGBH). Both series explore experimentally how ancient civilizations achieved notable constructions without modern machinery and construction methods. Each episode has guest experts who are challenged to develop and implement methods that may have been used. The original series was produced with the BBC and fully compiled in 1997 (although some episodes had been produced much earlier) and the second series was produced with Channel Four of the UK and fully compiled in 2000.</Overview>
<id>83797</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>248282</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Robinsons: Lost in Space</SeriesName>
<IMDB_ID>tt0777269</IMDB_ID>
<id>248282</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>90471</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Islands</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/90471-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>A hurricane nearly sinks the United World, a ship holding 40 teenagers from all around the world. Most of them flee the ship in lifeboats, however the evacuating children are not counted and five are left behind. The storm blows the battered sailing ship across a reef into the lagoon of an island.

The island, Tambu, ruled by a supposedly 200 year old immortal tyrant called "Q", who came to the island on one of several ships originally bound for New Holland. In the center of the island is a valley in which the descendants of the original ship still live, in the manner of an 18th century colonial community. Adjacent to Tambu is a smaller island, Malo, which is a barren wasteland. It is noteworthy because of a lagoon where prisoners are forced to dive for a "blue weed" which, according to the people of Tambu, is refined into a powder which the Q uses to extend his life.

The children befriend a local family, the Quinns, who help them remain hidden on the island in a swamp avoided by locals because it is, according to local myth, inhabited by the ghosts of the dead. Most of the episode storylines pit the children against the Q, who fears their knowledge of the outside world is a threat to his dominion of Tambu.</Overview>
<id>90471</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73162</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Secret Of Lost Creek</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>1992-02-01</FirstAired>
<id>73162</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73549</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lost Saucer</SeriesName>
<Overview>More dreck from uber-potheads Sid and Marty Kroft. The plot: Jim Neighbors and Ruth Buzzi play two cornball alien robots that befriend two children who have stowed aboard their UFO. Along with their half-horse/half-dog, Dorsey, the bumbling duo travel through time in a series of WACKY adventures, attempting to return the children to their appropriate planet and year. Think Land of the Lost, only with Gomer Pyle robots in place of dinosaurs. A disaster of a show that only a seven year old could appreciate.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1975-09-01</FirstAired>
<id>73549</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73420</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Finder of Lost Loves</SeriesName>
<Overview>Devastated by the death of his wife, Cary Maxwell dedicates himself to investigative work as a detective specializing in finding vanished lovers. His assignments are elusive, unpredictable and sometimes dangerous when the lost lover does not wish to be found.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1984-09-01</FirstAired>
<id>73420</id>
</Series>
</Data>